[
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "Which would be the least effective muscle to address for Plantarfascitis?",
    "options": {
      "a": "hamstrings",
      "b": "gastrocnemius",
      "c": "tibialis anterior",
      "d": "tibialis posterior"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "A major Lymph Plexus is found where?",
    "options": {
      "a": "foot",
      "b": "eyes",
      "c": "brainstem",
      "d": "spinal cord"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "The conception vessel rules which?",
    "options": {
      "a": "yin organs",
      "b": "the yang organs",
      "c": "neither"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "Which muscle does not assist with respiration?",
    "options": {
      "a": "scalenes",
      "b": "external intercostals",
      "c": "rhomboids"
    },
    "correct_option": "c",
    "correct_answer_text": "rhomboids"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "Which is a phasic muscle?",
    "options": {
      "a": "gluteus maximus",
      "b": "scalenes",
      "c": "levator scapula"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "The Vagus nerve does which to the heart rate?",
    "options": {
      "a": "increases the heart rate",
      "b": "decreases the heart rate",
      "c": "no effect on heart rate heart rate"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "Where are Erythrocytes formed?",
    "options": {
      "a": "red bone marrow",
      "b": "liver",
      "c": "yellow bone marrow A man has been smoking for 30 years. He wakes up repeatedly at 3am. He wants to stop taking laxatives and he has a heavy chest cough."
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "Which meridians would you address first in treating him?",
    "options": {
      "a": "HT/SI",
      "b": "LU/LI",
      "c": "ST/SP A man has been smoking for 30 years. He wakes up repeatedly at 3am. He wants to stop taking laxatives and he has a heavy chest cough."
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "Which is the mother of the involved element?",
    "options": {
      "a": "earth",
      "b": "metal",
      "c": "wood",
      "d": "fire A man has been smoking for 30 years. He wakes up repeatedly at 3am. He wants to stop taking laxatives and he has a heavy chest cough."
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "What other symptoms might he have?",
    "options": {
      "a": "premature balding",
      "b": "adult acne"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": "adult acne"
  }
]